## VINCE COGHLAN

1938 Spruce St #4 • Boulder, CO 80302 Cell: (303) 242-9122 • vince.coghlan@colorado.edu

## **STATEMENT**

To gain experience in a position that challenges my ability, intellect and resolve and offers the necessary skills to further my interests. I consider any opportunity, failure or not, an advancement of my career and a betterment of myself.

## **EDUCATION & HONORS**

University of Colorado at Boulder Class of 2015 Bachelor of Science in Electrical and Computer Engineering - Power Track Bachelor of Science in Computer Science - Systems Track Cumulative GPA: 3.758/4.0 High School Graduate - Aspen High School	2011-2015 Expected 2016 Expected 2016 As of March 2015 2010
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE	
Summer intern at Kyrus Technology in Denver Colorado, a computer security firm. At Kyrus I wrote software, designed a system as part of a team, and debugged hardware and software.	2014
System admin and technical support for the CU electrical department	2014-2015
Research Assistant - CU Boulder	2012
Intern, Board Operator, and Radio Personality - KSPN - Aspen, CO	2010-2011
SKILLS & CERTIFICATIONS	
Certified SolidWorks Associate	2011
Competent Programmer in a Variety of Languages	2015
RELAVANT COURSEWORK	
ECEN 2020, 2250, 2260, 2270, 2350, 3000, 3250, 3350, 3400, 3810, 4517, 4797, 5018 - Embedded Systems, Circuits I & II, Design Lab, Digital Logic, Microelectronics, Fields & Waves, Game Theory, Power Electronics, Power & Photovoltaic Lab.	2011-2015

## **EXTRACURRICULAR**

Avid Guitarist of 10 Years and Valve Amplifier Enthusiast	2004-2015
Passionate Snowboarder and Devoted Homebrewer	2013-2015